TREVON COSTA

CONTACT

(647) 215 - 7007



trevonccg@hotmail.com



Toronto, ON 👂



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ trevon-costa-9a6073219/

EDUCATION

COMPUTER PROGRAMMING AND ANALYSIS (T177)

George Brown College, Toronto

Developing the skills and techniques required for software application development and testing. 2020-2022

BUSINESS COURSES

Humber College, Toronto

Marketing Fundamentals, Introduction to Business. Mathematics of Finance 2018

KEY SKILLS

Determination

Time management

Communication

Ability to work under pressure

Organization

Planning

Creativity

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Extremely motivated Software Development Student with 2 years of studying at George Brown College. Currently working part-time as a merchandiser and providing customer service. Seeking opportunities to work in the Software Development field to gain experience and skills to continue growing professionally and personally. Accustomed to being well-organized and goal focused to complete projects on time. Looking to learn and help make an impact with my work.

EXPERIENCE

STUDENT - COURSES

George Brown College / Toronto / Jan 2020 - Present

- Mobile Application Development (iOS/Android)
- Full Stack Development
- Capstone Project
- Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning with Python
- Application Development using Java
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Agile Software Development
- **DEVOPS**

MERCHANDISER

Shoppers Drug Mart / Toronto / June 2018 - Present

- Responsible for effectively resolving customer issues utilizing effective problem-solving techniques.
- Provide support via telephone, answering customer queries regarding the products and services.
- Proactively identifying areas of improvement throughout the workplace which result in productivity gain.
- Perform designated opening and closing procedures and assist team members with remaining work as required.

TECHNOLOGIES

- C# / Java (Object-Oriented)
- Node.js
- Agile Methodologies

Data Structures and

- Python
- Algorithms

- JavaScript
- DevOps

Spring

And more!

REFERENCES

Available upon request.